The Matrix Revisited is a documentary film directed by Josh Oreck.
The film goes behind the scenes of the 1999 sci-fi movie The Matrix.
Self - Neo, played by Keanu Reeves.
Self - Agent Smith, played by Hugo Weaving.
Self - Trinity, played by Carrie-Anne Moss.
Self - Morpheus, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Self - President, Worldwide Theatrical Production, Warner
Bros., played by Lorenzo di Bonaventura.
Self - Producer, played by Joel Silver.
The Matrix Revisited is a 2001 American documentary film about
the production of the 1999 film The Matrix.
It was released on DVD and VHS on November 20, 2001, by Warner Home Video.
The film explores themes of behind the scenes, fan
culture, visual effect, making of.